Question :
Kostya likes the number 4 much. Of course! This number has such a lot of properties, like:
	• Four is the smallest composite number;
	• It is also the smallest Smith number;
	• The smallest non-cyclic group has four elements;
	• Four is the maximal degree of the equation that can be solved in radicals;
	• There is four-color theorem that states that any map can be colored in no more than four colors in such a way that no two adjacent regions are colored in the same color;
	• Lagrange's four-square theorem states that every positive integer can be written as the sum of at most four square numbers;
	• Four is the maximum number of dimensions of a real division algebra;
	• In bases 6 and 12, 4 is a 1-automorphic number;
	• And there are a lot more cool stuff about this number!
Impressed by the power of this number, Kostya has begun to look for occurrences of four anywhere. He has a list of T integers, for each of them he wants to calculate the number of occurrences of the digit 4 in the decimal representation. He is too busy now, so please help him.
Input
The first line of input consists of a single integer T, denoting the number of integers in Kostya's list.
Then, there are T lines, each of them contain a single integer from the list.
Output
Output T lines. Each of these lines should contain the number of occurences of the digit 4 in the respective integer from Kostya's list.
Constraints
	• 1 ≤ T ≤ 105
	• (Subtask 1): 0 ≤ Numbers from the list ≤ 9 - 33 points.
	• (Subtask 2): 0 ≤ Numbers from the list ≤ 109 - 67 points.
Example
Input:544747422866644081
Output:40110

From <https://www.codechef.com/problems/LUCKFOUR> 


Answer:
#include <iostream>
using namespace std;

int main() {
	int n,temp,t,rem,cnt=0;
	cin>>t;
	while(t--){
	    cin>>n;
	    temp=n;
	    while(temp!=0){
	        rem=temp%10;
	        temp/=10;
	        if(rem==4)
	        cnt++;
	    }
	    cout<<cnt<<endl;
	    cnt=0;
	}
	
	return 0;
}
